<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Yohannes&#39; Tech Blog</title>
    <link>https://youhengzhou.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Yohannes&#39; Tech Blog</description>
    <image>
      <title>Yohannes&#39; Tech Blog</title>
      <url>https://youhengzhou.github.io/blog/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://youhengzhou.github.io/blog/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://youhengzhou.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The best ideas arise from a passionate interest in commonplace things</title>
      <link>https://youhengzhou.github.io/blog/posts/03-best-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youhengzhou.github.io/blog/posts/03-best-ideas/</guid>
      <description>Foreword So I decided to try my hand at writing analytical essays. I took this topic from the GRE practice and sample essays booklet: The best ideas arise from a passionate interest in commonplace things. And I promise you I had only briefly looked at the first 3 lines on the official solution for a level 6 essay, before realizing my conversational/stream of consciousness vocabulary was not up to par.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to start a consultancy company</title>
      <link>https://youhengzhou.github.io/blog/posts/02-consulting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youhengzhou.github.io/blog/posts/02-consulting/</guid>
      <description>Part 1. Goal We know that every large goal starts off with a series of small goals. And even before that, every consequential result starts off with a concrete goal in mind. Actions that lead to that result only happen because of the pre-existence of that established goal.
The goal of this design document is to start a consultancy company. But more importantly, the goal of this experiment in starting a consultancy company is to learn the philosophy of consultancy and apply it to the struggles we have right now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding recursion and the limits of intelligence</title>
      <link>https://youhengzhou.github.io/blog/posts/01-recursion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youhengzhou.github.io/blog/posts/01-recursion/</guid>
      <description>Part 1. Introduction Recursion is a common pattern in programming. It occurs on many algorithm problems mostly relating to trees and graphs.
Recursion also seems to be one of those algorithms in programming where people either “get it” or “don’t get it.” Some people with experience would find it trivial, but it would seem almost impossible for beginner programmers or the layperson who had no prior experience with programming.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
